[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these terms refers to armpit hair?", "correct_answer": "Axillary hair", "incorrect_answers": ["Pubic hair", "Guard hair", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1993 movie Jurassic Park was produced by Steven Spielberg.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What American state, known also as the Silver State, is named after a weather condition?", "correct_answer": "Nevada", "incorrect_answers": ["Wyoming", "Colorado", "Oklahoma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first person to study the shape of a raindrop in 1898?", "correct_answer": "Philipp Lenard", "incorrect_answers": ["Philipp Drimsev", "Allton Kertsky", "Raymond Hasdroff"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Academy Award did the 1979 science fiction movie Alien receive?", "correct_answer": "Best Visual Effects", "incorrect_answers": ["Best Art Direction", "All of these", "Best Cinematography"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the following is not said to be haunted by the ghost of Abraham Lincoln?", "correct_answer": "The Lincoln Memorial.", "incorrect_answers": ["Fords Theatre.", "The White House.", "The family home in Springfield, Illinois."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although the first paperback books were published in Germany, it was in England that the paperback book first became very popular. This is considered the first paperback novel.", "correct_answer": "Pelham by Edward Bulwer-Lytton", "incorrect_answers": ["Robinson Crusoe by Daniel Defoe", "A Tale of Two Cities by Charles Dickens", "The Adventures of Tom Thumb by Brigham Wise-Dunne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Humans have much smaller amount of hair follicles in their skin per unit area than other primates.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What texture does Gruyere cheese traditionally have?", "correct_answer": "Hard", "incorrect_answers": ["Semi-hard", "Creamy", "Soft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The design of the Japanese fictional monster Godzilla was based on the characteristics of which dinosaur?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Stegosaurus", "Tyrannosaurus", "Iguanodon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin C is necessary for the production of this protein in the human body.", "correct_answer": "Collagen", "incorrect_answers": ["Cytokine", "Fibrin", "Opsin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Purple Haze is a song by what famous musician?", "correct_answer": "Jimi Hendrix", "incorrect_answers": ["John Lennon", "Jim Morrison", "Janis Joplin"]}]